Do you work for the news?
你是做新闻报道工作的吗?
Yes. I do. I'm a reporter.
Yes. 我是. 我是记者.
Where's the camera?
摄像机在哪儿?
Oh,I'm not a TV reporter.
Oh, 我不是电视记者.
-I'm a radio reporter. -Oh.
-我是个电台记者. -Oh.
Are you disappointed?
你失望了吗?
Did something happen?
出了什么事吗?
Do you mean,like a fire?
你的意思是, 类似于火灾?
No. I'm doing an interview.
No. 我要进行一个采访
That's part of my job,too.
那是我工作的一部分, too.
How come you're a reporter?
你是怎么成为一名记者的?
Oh, I like this job.
Oh, 我喜欢这份工作.
I used to work in an office.I hated that.
我以前的工作坐在办公室. 我讨厌那样.
Yeah?
Yeah. I worked in the mailroom.
Yeah. 那时我在收发室工作.
I was in that one room all day,you know?
我在一个房子里呆一整天, 你知道吗?
So I quit that job.
所以我辞了那个工作.
Guess what I did next.
猜猜我接下来做了什么.
What?
做什么?
I worked in a place where they raised rats for laboratories.
我在一个为实验室养老鼠的地方工作.
Really?
真的吗?
Yeah.
Cool.
Then I went to college.Then I got this job.
然后我读了大学. 再然后我得到了这份工作.
How does that work?
那东西怎么工作?
Do you want me to show you?
你想要我给你演示一下吗?
Come on. We'll do an interview.
Come on. 我们进行一次采访.